ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
It stopped.
You indeed made the thunder
and lightning gale on purpose.
How dare you set me up?
Although I don't have strong power,
luckily, I'm wise.
Don't waste your efforts.
You can't swap our souls
just by doing this.
Could it be…
The lightning.
That's right.
There must be lightning to swap our souls.
Fortunately, I figured it out
a little bit earlier than you.
It's just a little trick.
What's so hard about it?
It's just lightning.
I'll just summon it up again.
You can do nothing about it, right?
You can't use
your magic power anymore, right?
You were so arrogant just now.
I’m not afraid to tell you
that no matter how powerful you are,
as long as you’re inside
this loser body of mine,
you won't be able to do anything.
I won't be able to do anything?
What's there to be proud of?
Thank you.
Swap it back now
or I'll kill you right now.
You…
How dare you be rude to my lord?
Shangque, how dare you?
My lord, this fairy has offended
Heaven's authority.
What should we do to her?
Lock up this audacious little fairy!
- Yes.
- How dare you?
Let go of me! Do you know who I am?
- Greetings, my lord.
Get up.
You don't have to kneel. Get up.
So being the Moon Supreme seems dignified.
No wonder Dongfang Qingcang
always looks like he's a great man.
- Greetings, my lord.
Get up. There's no need to kneel.
- Thank you, my lord.
My lord, it's almost time.
Please go to the main hall
to attend the ceremony.
Ceremony?
What ceremony?
I…
I'm busy with affairs and can't recall it.
My lord.
Today is the ceremony held by ministers
for your return to Cangyan Sea
and officially taking over the Moon Tribe.
They are all waiting for you
in the main hall.
I just have to pretend to be
the Moon Supreme.
Let me fool them first.
I remember now. Let's go.
Let me guess.
Is the main hall on the left or right?
My lord.
You lead the way.
What are you waiting for? Hurry up and go.
Yes.
- My lord.
SILENT MOON PALACE, CANGYAN SEA
- Greetings, my lord.
Please rise.
To congratulate my lord
on regaining control of the Moon Tribe,
I have prepared a great gift.
Bring him up.
He's…
My lord.
For 30,000 years,
the Fairy Tribe has repeatedly invaded
the Moon Tribe.
They've been trying to kill us.
Recently, they've sent spies
to Cangyan Sea
to spy on the military.
You said he's from the Fairy Tribe?
That's right.
This man is the leader of the spies.
He was captured by me.
I…
This is my welcome ceremony.
What are you doing here with a fairy?
I'm presenting the spy
to follow the ancient ritual
of making a fairy sacrifice to our flag
and celebrating your return
with the blood of fairies.
Please do it, my lord.
You want me to kill him?
I mean,
this is a great day.
It’s not good to see blood, right?
My lord.
On such a joyous occasion,
what could be a better boost to our morale
than your victory over a fairy?
My lord, please kill the fairy
to boost the morale of the army.
I mean,
if you're willing to submit
to Cangyan Sea,
I'll spare your life.
How is that?
Surrender.
How dare you?
How dare you desecrate my lord?
My lord,
there's no need to talk to him anymore.
Kill him.
- Kill him!
All right.
You have the courage and grace.
I'll fulfill your wish.
Someone.
Take him away.
No need.
What kind of trick are you trying to play?
As a member of the Fairy Tribe,
I'm loyal to Shuiyuntian.
I’d rather die than surrender
to the Moon Tribe.
Although we are at odds with Shuiyuntian,
we also admire a true, resolute warrior.
If you had become a traitor today,
I would have beheaded you on the spot.
But you're willing to die and not give in.
That has changed my mind.
Send him back to Shuiyuntian.
My lord.
I'm the Moon Supreme of the three realms.
If I kill a true warrior
who has no power to fight back today,
wouldn't the three realms
hold me up to ridicule if word gets out?
If I want to kill,
I'll do it on the battlefield righteously.
You can go now.
Go back and tell Lord Yunzhong.
When we meet in future battles,
I won't be lenient.
Take him away.
- Yes.
My goodness.
These people are so scary.
They fight and kill.
They look fierce and vicious.
It doesn’t seem easy
to be the Moon Supreme.
My lord,
you still have some matters to handle.
- Do you want to--
- What did you say?
I'm tired. I need to go back and rest now.
Yes.
Stop right there.
I want to see the Moon Supreme.
People from Shuiyuntian are so daring
that you're still thinking
of throwing yourself at my lord even now.
What a pity.
How could my lord like
such a mediocre woman?
That's right.
Let go of me.
How dare you trick me?
Damn you. Open the door.
My lord, take a good rest.
Wait.
Who are they?
My lord.
They are your guards.
I know you're very powerful,
but you've just returned to Cangyan Sea.
Everything is still in turmoil.
I'm afraid there might be a hidden plot.
So I've specially arranged--
With so many men in my bedroom,
how can I possibly rest?
Yes.
Stand down.
- Yes.
I'm in his body.
How can I go back to Shuiyuntian?
How will people believe
that Dongfang Qingcang
swapped bodies with a little fairy?
What should I do?
Even if they do believe you,
how can you prove
that you are not from the Moon Tribe
or a spy of the Moon Tribe?
- My lord.
- My goodness.
My lord.
She's the woman brought back
by the Moon Supreme.
- If you kill her--
- If we don’t kill her and she tells on us,
neither of us can survive.
My lord.
- Come on.
- My lord.
- We are here to serve you in bed.
- Come on.
All of you, get out.
My lord.
Let me serve you, my lord.
Out of the way!
Stand down!
- Yes.
Why didn't my lord let us serve him?
That's right.
He threw me out.
- That's odd.
- We shouldn't have come here.
What’s going on?
Lord Shangque.
We went to the chamber
to serve Moon Supreme just now,
but unexpectedly, he threw us out.
You are his only former minister.
You must know him well.
Have we done something wrong
that angered him?
What you don't know is that
he has never been close to women.
If you are not called in the future,
don't go serve him on your own accord.
Lord Shangque, the Moon Supreme
invites you into his room.
Now?
Yes.
- I heard it too.
- Is it true?
- Is that true?
- That's impossible.
Is that true?
Shut up.
If you dare to talk nonsense again,
I'll cut off your tongues.
Greetings, my lord.
Come here.
I'm willing to die for you, my lord.
I just want to ask you something
about the old days.
Why do you look so reluctant?
What do you want to ask me?
Let me ask you.
In your eyes,
what kind of person did I use to be?
Did I have any special hobbies
and preferences?
How did I act in general?
Tell me what you think of me.
You can say anything you want.
Why are you asking this?
Actually, I suffered some injuries
during the battle.
My memory has been affected.
I can't remember many old things.
Has your magic power been damaged?
Magic power?
Of course it's damaged.
In fact, that day in Wind Plain,
I used up all my strength
to deter Xunfeng and the others.
Now, my power is intermittent.
I'm afraid I'm no match for
the Kings of North and South You.
My lord.
Does anyone else know about this?
If there is someone else who knows,
I'll go and silence him.
Silence him? Is it so serious?
No, you're the only one who knows now.
I'm afraid you have forgotten.
Cangyan Sea has always admired the strong.
The two kings have surrendered to you
for the exact fear of your great power.
If they know that your power is damaged,
they will turn against you
and take your place.
In that case,
my lord, you'll be
in an even more dangerous situation.
What about your power?
Can you defeat them?
Can you protect me?
I can't win if I fight alone.
Why are you here?
What are you waiting for? Help…
My lord.
You…
Get out.
How did you get out of Wind Prison?
I’m going to make out
with the Moon Supreme now.
Are you going to watch from there?
You can’t leave!
Help me!
I'm leaving.
Get up.
Don’t come up.
Help me!
I said there should be lightning.
You've kissed and hugged me.
Are we swapped back?
Why don't you just accept the reality
and keep the status quo for now?
Keep the status quo?
You're getting used to it so fast.
That's right.
You can even use my body
to find a man to sleep with.
You should be happy.
Should I look for you
rather than someone else?
That's right.
You always pretend
to be so proud and aloof.
I didn't realize you had a lot of women.
Have I ever had a woman?
Yes, you do.
When I say no, I mean no.
You're still pretending.
What is there to deny?
I don't need to prove my innocence to you.
That's right.
Anyway, you already said
you don't have any love for me.
Your affair is none of my business.
I'm not even interested.
It’s good that you know.
You still have the energy
to bicker with me.
Are you aware of the situation
that you and I are in?
Stupid woman.
You've been pretending to be me all day.
Didn't you notice?
Once someone finds out
I've swapped bodies with you
and I'm a powerless loser now,
you and I will both die.
It's just a fluke
that you're still alive.
You’re scaring me on purpose, right?
So what should we do now?
Swap back.
I told you there's no lightning now.
I have great power.
Now that you've taken my body,
you can't even make a mere lightning bolt…
That's right. I'll try.
What a loser.
It's not the first day
for you to know this.
You can't call up lightning either now,
can you?
Don’t just accuse me.
You should think of a way too.
I watched the sky when I came.
In three days,
there will be thunder and lightning.
At that time, lightning will show up.
However,
during these three days,
you must be careful
with your words and actions.
Do as I tell you to do.
Remember.
If you reveal a flaw in front of anyone,
both of us will die
without a burial place.
Do you understand?
Are you sure about this?
- Come on.
- I beg you.
- Don't be shy.
- Get out.
- No need to serve me.
- Come on.
- All of you, get out.
- My lord.
You said the Destiny Book
was with Dongfang Qingcang?
I saw it clearly.
I couldn't be mistaken.
Master.
Dongfang Qingcang must have confirmed
through the Destiny Book
that Red Spirit is the reincarnation
of God of War.
But why didn't he just take the spirit
and unseal 100,000 soldiers?
Something must be in his way.
It seems that if we want to retrieve
the Destiny Book and the goddess,
we must first get rid
of Dongfang Qingcang.
But he's very powerful.
We are no match for him.
Profound as his power is,
he can't resist the erosion
of evil spirits.
The evil spirit has boundless power,
but Dongfang Qingcang is alert
and suspicious by nature.
All of our spies
have been cleared out by him.
No one can get close to him.
There is one more person who can help me.
DARK PINE FOREST, CANGYAN SEA
Lord Xunfeng,
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Hold your head high.
Show imposing and condescending manners.
How was that?
Watch your eyes.
When you don't know
how to deal with people,
just stare at them coldly
and make them feel intimidated.
Like this.
What are you laughing at?
I just think it's funny
to see my face
looking so terrifying.
I'm just a little fairy.
I basically nod and bow to people.
I don't know how to be imposing,
not to mention condescending.
I'm tired.
Fine.
You just have to remember.
You should be afraid of no one
and trust no one.
What about Shangque?
Isn't Shangque your confidant?
Can’t you trust him either?
I only trust myself.
If I were you,
I would tell Shangque about the body swap
so that we can work together.
I'm sure we'll find a way
to swap our bodies back.
How naive.
The strong is admired in Cangyan Sea.
If word of the body swap gets out,
I'm afraid everyone would want
to challenge you
to become the new Moon Supreme.
You can’t activate the power in my body.
Not to mention Shangque or Xunfeng,
even a mere moon warrior
can easily kill you at that time.
I don’t think so.
I think Shangque
is quite affectionate to you.
He will never betray you.
What do you know?
I just know.
You don't understand the heart
and emotions.
That's why you don't know.
Big Blockhead.
Let me ask you.
Is there a rule in Cangyan Sea that says
the stronger winner must kill the loser?
There is no such rule.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
I'm just asking.
Tell me.
You asked me to say it.
Don’t turn your back on me if I do.
I just think it's strange.
If you didn't have to kill him,
why did you kill your father
after you won against him?
Lord of Haishi,
you came here late at night.
What for?
I heard that Dongfang Qingcang
has come back from the dead
and returned to Cangyan Sea.
I'm worried about you.
That's why I dropped by.
I was ordered
to be the Moon Supreme to quell crises.
Even if Dongfang Qingcang
is concerned about this,
he can't find any reason to kill me.
Thirty thousand years ago,
if the Wind Warriors led by you
had helped in time,
Dongfang Qingcang wouldn't
have been left alone on the battlefield.
If Dongfang Qingcang pursues the case
and claims that you had been disobedient,
how will you defend yourself,
Lord Xunfeng?
However,
you and Dongfang Qingcang
are blood-related.
If you can proactively show kindness
and put aside your hatred,
maybe Dongfang Qingcang
will forget about the past.
After all, 30,000 years have passed.
You should have let go of the grudge
of your father's death.
It's unforgivable whatsoever.
How can I just let go of it?
Even if I lose my life,
I shall kill him with my own hands
to console my father's spirit.
Why bother, Lord Xunfeng?
From the day he killed my father,
our fates have been sealed.
Either he dies or I die.
Back then, it was you
who helped me build Haishi.
I'll always remember your kindness.
Now, if you have made up your mind,
I'll do everything I can
to help you achieve your wish.
I’m afraid it won't be easy
to kill him.
Lord Xunfeng, do you not trust me?
Have you forgotten, Lord Xunfeng?
Over 30,000 years ago,
it was me who helped you plan
the counterbalance between
the Kings of North and South You
to save Ninth You.
Now,
I can also help you kill Dongfang Qingcang
to avenge the death of your father.
Fortunately,
you've been planning in secret
all these years.
If it weren't for your foresight
and maneuvering,
I'm afraid the foundation
built by my father
would have been taken away
by the two kings.
It's just that Dongfang Qingcang
is very powerful
and ruthless.
Without the means to kill him in one blow,
you must not act rashly
and alert him.
I'll help you kill Dongfang Qingcang.
However,
we have to consider this in the long run
and wait for the right time.
Father!
Only by killing him
will I be able to secure the position
as the new Moon Supreme.
What's so strange about that?
I never thought the rumor
that you killed your father is true.
Then why isn't there any trace of pain
or regret on your face
when you mention it?
Regret?
Why should I regret it?
He's your father.
So what?
I've always dreamed
of having a family and parents.
You had a father,
but you killed him with your own hands.
People say you're a coldhearted jerk
who doesn’t recognize your own family.
I thought people got you wrong.
That's right.
I'm a jerk.
Now,
if you don't want to die,
you must learn how to be a jerk.
What are you doing?
Come here.
Let go.
I'm a beautiful fairy with a good heart.
I don’t want to be a jerk.
Get out of here.
Watch her.
Don't let her in without my order.
- Yes.
You…
Go.